<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on rosshudson.co.uk</title>
    <link>https://rosshudson.co.uk/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on rosshudson.co.uk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rosshudson.co.uk/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Wankie: How To Make Your Own Off-Brand Winkie</title>
      <link>https://rosshudson.co.uk/posts/wankie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosshudson.co.uk/posts/wankie/</guid>
      <description>On Ep. 114 of CheapShow, Paul and Eli found a bizarre French single promoting a failed electronic pin badge called Winkie.
It&amp;rsquo;s just a badge that alternates between a red and green LED every second. It sounds incredibly dull but somehow it&amp;rsquo;s not.
I found myself so far down the rabbit hole, I decided to design a clone.
I present to you, Wankie:
This post will go through how I designed it and how to make your own (if you can etch your own circuit boards&amp;hellip;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Takin&#39; Me Away From You Train Chords</title>
      <link>https://rosshudson.co.uk/posts/taking-me-away-from-you-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosshudson.co.uk/posts/taking-me-away-from-you-train/</guid>
      <description>A nice little song by a seemingly overlooked folk singer named Len Chandler.
 These chords are transcribed from his appearance on Pete Seeger&amp;rsquo;s Rainbow Quest which I think is the best recording of the song. Len released a few studio albums during the mid-late 60s but they all sound a bit forced and over-produced to me - the live recordings he appears on are well worth a listen
While this particular song is more personal and sentimental, he first became known as a protest singer during the civil rights movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Strawberry Session Mead</title>
      <link>https://rosshudson.co.uk/posts/simple-strawberry-mead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosshudson.co.uk/posts/simple-strawberry-mead/</guid>
      <description>My recipe for a strawberry hydromel (low alcohol mead). Ready to drink in 3-4 weeks.
 2kg strawberries
Frozen or fresh will do. Hull and then chop them into small (~2cm) chunks and place them into a pot. Cover with water and bring to a boil then simmer until the water is a deep red and strawberries have lost most of their colour - about 25 minutes. Strain through a sieve and/or cheesecloth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Apple Wine</title>
      <link>https://rosshudson.co.uk/posts/simple-apple-wine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosshudson.co.uk/posts/simple-apple-wine/</guid>
      <description>Here is my recipe for the simplest, cheapest way to make a nice apple wine. It comes out between 10-12% ABV and tastes pretty good.
Yields 5l (UK gallon).
 5l of apple juice from concentrate
It shouldn&amp;rsquo;t contain any additives, except ascorbic acid which is just the posh name for vitamin C. In my experience the price/quality doesn&amp;rsquo;t impact on the final product, so I&amp;rsquo;d reccomend just using supermakret own brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helen Wheels</title>
      <link>https://rosshudson.co.uk/posts/helen-wheels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosshudson.co.uk/posts/helen-wheels/</guid>
      <description>This project started off with the idea of creating a chatbot that speaks through a typewriter. I&amp;rsquo;ve not got round to making the chatbot part yet, but I probably will in the future. The major hurdle of course was making the typing work.
Here it is booting up:
Your browser does not support the video tag.  Concept The typewriter I got uses matrix polling to determine what keys to type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LC29 B&amp;W Film Developer Review</title>
      <link>https://rosshudson.co.uk/posts/lc29-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosshudson.co.uk/posts/lc29-review/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve used Ilford LC29 almost exclusively for a year now so I thought it would be a good time to detail my experience with it since there doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be much love for it out there.
I think it&amp;rsquo;s a great solution for most casual photographers - shooting a few rolls a month at varying speeds and not having a lot of time to mess around.
 It&amp;rsquo;s economical The going rate is around £20 for 500ml.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>