<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>home on rosshudson.co.uk</title>
    <link>https://rosshudson.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in home on rosshudson.co.uk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rosshudson.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Takin&#39; Me Away From You Train</title>
      <link>https://rosshudson.co.uk/chords/taking-me-away-from-you-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosshudson.co.uk/chords/taking-me-away-from-you-train/</guid>
      <description>Transcribed from episode 22 of Pete Seeger&amp;rsquo;s Rainbow Quest
Len Chandler is a seemingly lost gem from the 60s folk revival. His studio albums are a bit forced and over-produced, though the live recordings he appears on are excellent
While this particlar song is more personal and sentimental, he was also very politically conscious. Here&amp;rsquo;s a verse he added to Which Side Are You On?:
 Come all you bourgeois black men With all your excess fat A few days in the county jail Will sure get rid of that</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Strawberry Session Mead</title>
      <link>https://rosshudson.co.uk/simple-strawberry-mead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosshudson.co.uk/simple-strawberry-mead/</guid>
      <description>How to make a simple low-alcohol strawberry mead (hydromel)
(This recipe assumes some basic homebrewing experience. See this guide for a more general overview)
Equipment:
 5l (UK Gallon) demijohn/fermentation bucket Airlock Siphon w/ bottling wand Bottles Cheesecloth/fine muslin bag Potato masher  Ingredients:
 2kg fresh strawberries Honey (ASDA own-brand, &amp;ldquo;pure Honey&amp;rdquo; 908g) Water Wine yeast  Method:
 Prepare the strawberries Hull (chop the heads off) all the strawberries then give them a quick wash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Apple Wine</title>
      <link>https://rosshudson.co.uk/simple-apple-wine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosshudson.co.uk/simple-apple-wine/</guid>
      <description>The simplest, cheapest, idiot-proofiest way to make a nice apple wine. (This recipe assumes some basic homebrewing experience. See this guide for a more general overview)
Equipment:
 5l (UK Gallon) demijohn/fermentation bucket Airlock Siphon w/ bottling wand Bottles  Ingredients:
 5l of cheap apple juice from concentrate with no additives except ascorbic acid (the expensive makes no difference to the final product) 600g sugar Wine yeast Black tea (optional)  Method:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helen Wheels</title>
      <link>https://rosshudson.co.uk/helen-wheels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosshudson.co.uk/helen-wheels/</guid>
      <description>This project started off with the idea of creating a chatbot that speaks through a typewriter. I&amp;rsquo;ve not got round to making the chatbot part yet, but I probably will in the future. The major hurdle of course was making the typing work.
Here it is booting up:
Your browser does not support the video tag.  Concept The typewriter I got uses matrix polling to determine what keys to type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LC29 B&amp;W Film Developer Review</title>
      <link>https://rosshudson.co.uk/lc29-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosshudson.co.uk/lc29-review/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve used Ilford LC29 almost exclusively for a year now so I thought it would be a good time to detail my experience with it since there doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be much love for it out there.
I think it&amp;rsquo;s a great solution for most casual photographers - shooting a few rolls a month at varying speeds and not having a lot of time to mess around.
 It&amp;rsquo;s economical The going rate is around £20 for 500ml.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>